RG 005:035, Office of the Governor: Thomas J. Meskill (1971-1975)
Connecticut State Library
- Series 7. Agency Files, 1971-1975
  - Transportation Department (Box A-854)
    - Subject Files (Box A-859)
      - Crisis Response Team (Box A-865)
      - Danbury – Airport (Box A-866)
      - Danbury - Bethel Transit District (Box A-866)
      - Davis-Bacon Act (Box A-866)
      - Day Trip Briefings (Box A-866)
      - Del-Gaudio (Box A-866)
      - Dial A Ride (Box A-866)
      - Diesel Cars to Go Gas Turbine (Box A-866)
      - East Haddam Land Sale (Box A-866)
      - East / West Highway (Box A-866)
      - Editorials (Box A-866)
      - Emergency Highway Energy Act (Box A-866)
      - Employment Emergency act (Box A-866)
      - Energy Crisis (Box A-866)
      - Enfield Suffield Bridge (Box A-866)
      - Environment (Box A-866)
      - Environmental Impact (Box A-866)
      - Federal Aid Highway (Box A-866)
      - Federal Aviation Administration (Box A-866)
      - Federal DOT, 2 folders (Box A-866)
      - Federal DOT Newsletter (Box A-866)
      - Federal Highway Act of 1973 (Box A-866)
      - Federal Legislation (Box A-866)
      - Federal / State (Box A-866)
      - Financial & Budgetary Reports, 2 folders (Box A-866)
      - Fire Chief Funds for Emergency Training (Box A-866)
      - Flood (Box A-866)
      - Fox File (Box A-866)
      - Freight (Box A-866)
      - Freight Car Shortage Testimony (Box A-866)
      - Funds (Box A-866)
      - "Gale Drive" (Box A-867)
      - Gasoline Shortage (Box A-867)
      - General Electric, 2 folders (Box A-867)
      - Glastonbury-Rocky Hill Ferry (Box A-867)
      - Gold Star Bridge (Box A-867)
      - Governor’s Northeast Rail Testimony (Box A-867)
      - Governor’s Representative for Highway Safety (Box A-867)
      - Governor’s Special Commission on the Financing of Mass Transportation (Box A-867)
      - Grade Crossing (Box A-867)
      - Grants to Towns (Box A-867)
      - Greater Bridgeport Transit (Box A-867)
      - Greater Hartford Chamber of Commerce ,Transit Committee (Box A-867)
      - Greater Hartford Transit (Box A-867)
      - Greater Hartford Transportation System (Box A-867)
      - Growth Centers (Box A-867)
      - Handicapped / Ramps (Box A-867)
      - Helicopters, 2 folders (Box A-867)
      - High Level Platforms (Box A-867)
      - High Speed (Box A-867)
      - High Speed Rail (Box A-867)
      - Highway Beautification (Box A-867)
      - Highways, Bureau of (Box A-867)
      - Highway Communication System (Box A-867)
      - Highway Construction Schedule (Box A-867)
      - Highway Fund (Box A-867)
      - Highway Fund (Box A-868)
      - Highway Fund, 1974 (Box A-868)
      - Highway Garages (Box A-868)
      - Highways (Interstate) General (Box A-868)
      - Highway Lighting (Box A-868)
      - Highway Maintenance (Box A-868)
      - Highway Research Board (Box A-868)
      - Highway Safety, 1973 September 27 (Box A-868)
      - Highway Safety (Box A-868)
      - Highway Safety Improvements (Box A-868)
      - Highway Trust (Box A-868)
      - Highway Workers (Box A-868)
      - Highways (Box A-868)
      - Highway (State Roads) General (Box A-868)
      - Hoover Crafts (Box A-868)
      - Interstate Commerce Act (Box A-868)
      - Interstate-84 (Box A-868)
      - Interstate-84 Canterbury (Box A-868)
      - Interstate-84 East (Box A-868)
      - Interstate-84 Waterbury (Box A-868)
      - Interstate-84 West (Waterbury), 2 folders (Box A-868)
      - Interstate-85 (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-91 (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-95 (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-95 Rest Stop (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-95 / West Haven High School (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-95 Connecticut Turnpike (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-291, 3 folders (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-291, 1973 July 31 (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-291 – Mayor Adams (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-291 – Mag Letter (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-291 Welles Petition (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-484 (Box A-869)
      - Interstate-684 (Box A-869)
      - Jet Port (Box A-870)
      - Kanell / Memos (Box A-870)
      - Kelsh (Box A-870)
      - Land Acquisition (Box A-870)
      - Land Use / Transportation Planning (Box A-870)
      - Laundry (Box A-870)
      - Lease (Box A-870)
      - Lease – New Haven (Box A-870)
      - Legislative Bulletin (Box A-870)
      - Legislation, 1973 (Box A-870)
      - Legislation, 1974 (Box A-870)
      - Legislation – Urban Mass & Passenger Inter-City (Box A-870)
      - Limited Access Highway (Box A-870)
      - Long Haul Support Program (Box A-870)
      - Long Island Sound Bridge (Box A-870)
      - Long Wharf Parking (Box A-870)
      - Lovers Leap Bridge (Box A-870)
      - Mass Transit Backer – Labels – Toby Moffett (Box A-870)
      - Mass Transit Legislation (Box A-870)
      - Mass Transit – Mag Letter, 1973 August (Box A-870)
      - Mass Transit – Printed Letter, 1974 February (Box A-870)
      - Mass Transportation Telegrams (Box A-870)
      - Master Plan, 1973 (Box A-870)
      - Master Plan, 1974 (Box A-870)
      - Memorandums (Box A-870)
      - Memos from Colin Pease (Box A-870)
      - Memos from Renee to Governor Meskill (Box A-870)
      - Memos to and from Sam Kanell (Box A-870)
      - Meriden – Markham Airport (Box A-870)
      - Merritt Parkway (Box A-871)
      - Merritt Parkway (Ex. Order), 1974 April (Box A-871)
      - Merritt Parkway Letter, 1973 December (Box A-871)
      - Merritt Parkway, 2 folders (Box A-871)
      - Merritt Parkway, 1973 November (Box A-871)
      - Merritt Parkway Rt. 80 – 25 (Box A-871)
      - Merritt – Thank You (Box A-871)
      - Metro Flight (Box A-871)
      - Minor Improvements (Box A-871)
      - Mohegan-Pequot Bridge (Box A-871)
      - Monorail, 2 folders (Box A-871)
      - Monorail – Mag Letter sent to Mayors (Box A-871)
      - Monorail, 1973 November 19 (Box A-871)
      - Montowese Street Bridge (Box A-871)
      - Motor Carriers (Box A-871)
      - Motor Transport, 2 folders (Box A-871)
      - Motorcycle (Box A-871)
      - Mt. Carmel Connector (Box A-871)
      - Mystic Oral School (Box A-871)
      - Mystic Seaport (Box A-871)
      - Nahum – Mini Buses (Box A-871)
      - National Highway Safety Bureau, 2 folders (Box A-871)
      - National Railroad Governing Board (Box A-871)
      - Needs Study (Box A-871)
      - Nepaug Dam (Box A-871)
      - New England Power Supply (Box A-871)
      - New England Rail Office (Box A-871)
      - NERC (Box A-871)
      - New Haven Bus Service (Box A-871)
      - New Haven Canal Line (Box A-871)
      - New Haven Line (Box A-871)
      - New Haven Railroad Terminal Building (Box A-871)
      - New Haven Water Co., 2 folders (Box A-871)
      - New Industries (G-E) (Box A-871)
      - New London / Coleman St. (Box A-871)
      - New York Giants Traffic Committee (Box A-872)
      - News Clippings, 2 folders (Box A-872)
      - News – D.O.T. (Box A-872)
      - News Releases - Misc. (Box A-872)
      - Newtown (Box A-872)
      - Niantic Bridge (Box A-872)
      - Noise (Box A-872)
      - Noise Pollution (Box A-872)
      - Norpax (Box A-872)
      - Northeast Corridor (Box A-872)
      - Northeast Rail Crisis Petitions (Box A-872)
      - Northeastern Railroad (Box A-872)
      - Nutmeg Inns (Box A-872)
      - Old Saybrook (Box A-872)
      - Organization Manuals (Box A-872)
      - Oxford Airport (Box A-872)
      - Oyster Bay Bridge (Box A-872)
      - Pacer – D.O.T., 2 folders (Box A-872)
      - Pamphlets (Box A-872)
      - Parking (Box A-872)
      - Penn Central (Box A-872)
      - Penn Central (Box A-873)
      - Penn Central Crisis (Box A-873)
      - Penn Central Freight Crisis (Box A-873)
      - Penn Central R. R. Strike (Box A-873)
      - Penn Central R. R. Transportation (Box A-873)
      - Personnel (Box A-873)
      - Podell Bill (Box A-873)
      - Pollution (Box A-873)
      - Poquonock River Bridge (Box A-873)
      - Position Papers – Transportation (Box A-873)
      - Postal Parking (Box A-873)
      - Power Facilities – Pfec 5612 – Wadsworth Bill (Box A-873)
      - Press Releases, 2 folders (Box A-873)
      - Project 59-105-0790 (Box A-873)
      - Projects, 1973-1974 (Box A-873)
      - Property Control (Box A-873)
      - Proposal for Bids (Box A-873)
      - Proposed Regional Rail Corp. (Box A-873)
      - Public Hearings (Box A-873)
      - Public Notices (Box A-873)
      - Public Utilities (Box A-873)
      - Rail Abandonment (Box A-874)
      - Rail Bus (Box A-874)
      - Rail Bus Demonstration (Box A-874)
      - Rail Clamdigger (Box A-874)
      - Rail Crisis Petitions (Box A-874)
      - Rail Crossing in New London – Feasibility Study (Box A-874)
      - Rail Freight (Box A-874)
      - Rail Line Route Abandonment (Box A-874)
      - Rail Motor Carriers (Box A-874)
      - Rail Passenger Service (Box A-874)
      - Rail Passenger Service Act of 1970 (Box A-874)
      - Rail Pax (Box A-874)
      - Rail Strike Information (Box A-874)
      - Rail Task Force (Box A-874)
      - Rail Testimony, 1974 March 11 (Box A-874)
      - Rail Transportation Committee (Box A-874)
      - Railroad – General Files (Box A-874)
      - Railroad Task Force (Box A-874)
      - Railroad Task Force – Exec. Order 24 (Box A-874)
      - Rapid Transit (Box A-874)
      - Regional Rail Act, 1973 (Box A-875)
      - Regional Rail Agency (Box A-875)
      - Renee (Box A-875)
      - Representative Mail (Box A-875)
      - Research (Box A-875)
      - Respiratory Health association Center (Box A-875)
      - Rest Areas (Box A-875)
      - Retirement (Box A-875)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box A-875)
      - Rights of Way (Box A-875)
      - Route 1 (Box A-875)
      - Route 2 (Box A-875)
      - Route 5 (Box A-875)
      - Route 6 (Box A-875)
      - Route 7 / Linear Park (Box A-875)
      - Route 7 (Box A-875)
      - Route 7 Special (Box A-875)
      - Route 8 (Box A-875)
      - Route 8 / Beaver Dam (Box A-875)
      - Route 9 (Box A-875)
      - Route 10, 2 folders (Box A-875)
      - Route 11 (Box A-875)
      - Route 12 (Box A-875)
      - Route 15 (Box A-875)
      - Route 17 (Box A-875)
      - Route 19 (Box A-875)
      - Route 20 (Box A-875)
      - Route 21 (Box A-875)
      - Route 22 (Box A-875)
      - Route 25 / Beachemin (Box A-875)
      - Route 25 (Box A-876)
      - Route 25 (Merritt) (Mrs. Eltrich) (Box A-876)
      - Route 27 (Box A-876)
      - Route 30 (Box A-876)
      - Route 32 (Box A-876)
      - Route 34 (Box A-876)
      - Route 35 (Box A-876)
      - Route 37 (Box A-876)
      - Route 39 (Box A-876)
      - Route 44 (Box A-876)
      - Route 45 (Box A-876)
      - Route 46 (Box A-876)
      - Route 47 (Box A-876)
      - Route 52 (Box A-876)
      - Route 53 (Box A-876)
      - Route 57 (Box A-876)
      - Route 58 (Box A-876)
      - Route 59 (Box A-876)
      - Route 63 (Box A-876)
      - Route 63 & 64 (Box A-876)
      - Route 66 (Box A-876)
      - Route 67 (Box A-876)
      - Route 68 (Box A-876)
      - Route 69 (Box A-876)
      - Route 70 (Box A-876)
      - Route 72 (Box A-876)
      - Route 75 (Box A-876)
      - Route 77 (Box A-876)
      - Route 78 (Box A-876)
      - Route 81 (Box A-876)
      - Route 82 (Box A-876)
      - Route 83 (Box A-876)
      - Route 84 (Box A-876)
      - Route 85 Project (Box A-876)
      - Route 95 (Box A-876)
      - Route 99 (Box A-876)
      - Route 101 (Box A-876)
      - Route 106 (Box A-876)
      - Route 108, 2 folders (Box A-876)
      - Route 110 (Box A-876)
      - Route 123 (Box A-876)
      - Route 124 (Box A-876)
      - Route 135 (Box A-876)
      - Route 136 (Box A-876)
      - Route 138 (Box A-876)
      - Route 140, 2 folders (Box A-876)
      - Route 142 (Box A-876)
      - Route 146 (Box A-876)
      - Route 153 (Box A-876)
      - Route 154, 2 folders (Box A-876)
      - Route 156 (Box A-876)
      - Route 159 (Box A-876)
      - Route 160 (Box A-876)
      - Route 161 (Box A-876)
      - Route 162 (Box A-876)
      - Route 171 (Box A-876)
      - Route 175 (Box A-876)
      - Route 177 (Box A-876)
      - Route 178 (Box A-876)
      - Route 190 (Box A-876)
      - Route 194 (Box A-876)
      - Route 195 (Box A-876)
      - Route 197 (Box A-876)
      - Route 229 (Box A-876)
      - Route 275 (Box A-876)
      - Route 318 (Box A-876)
      - Route 486 (Box A-876)
      - Route 649, 3 folders (Box A-876)
      - SST (Box A-877)
      - Safety Belt (Box A-877)
      - Safety Commission / Audit (Box A-877)
      - Saugatuck River Bridge – Westport (Box A-877)
      - Senate Testimony – Highway Bill – Transportation Fund (Box A-877)
      - Senior Citizens (Box A-877)
      - Signs & Billboards (Box A-877)
      - Sherwood Island Connector (Box A-877)
      - Shugrue, James – Memos (Box A-877)
      - Sikorsky Aircraft (Box A-877)
      - Sikorsky Memorial Airport – Bridgeport (Box A-877)
      - Silver Lane (Box A-877)
      - Silver Lane Widening (Box A-877)
      - South Street Bridge (Box A-877)
      - Southport Ticket Window Closing (Box A-877)
      - Speaking Engagements (Box A-877)
      - Speed Limits, 2 folders (Box A-877)
      - Snow Emergency (Box A-877)
      - Stamford Area Luncheon (Box A-877)
      - Stamford Project (Box A-877)
      - State Land (Box A-877)
      - State Legislation (Box A-877)
      - State Owned Vehicles (Box A-877)
      - State Pier (Box A-877)
      - State Planning Office (Box A-877)
      - State Truck Usage (Box A-877)
      - State Work Program, 1974 (Box A-877)
      - Stewart Air Force (Box A-877)
      - Stonington (Box A-877)
      - Surplus Property (Box A-877)
      - Task Force (Box A-878)
      - Testimony S-502 (Federal-Aid Highway Act 1973) (Box A-878)
      - Three Bears Rest. (Merritt Parkway) (Box A-878)
      - Ticket Window Closing (Box A-878)
      - Toll Investigation (Box A-878)
      - Topics (Box A-878)
      - Topics – Stamford (Box A-878)
      - Traffic Commission (Box A-878)
      - Traffic Commission Parade Route – Derby / Shelton (Box A-878)
      - Traffic Coordinating Committee (Box A-879)
      - Traffic Safety (Box A-879)
      - Traffic Signals (Box A-879)
        - (Box A-879)
      - Trains (Box A-879)
      - Transit District Development (Box A-879)
      - Transportation Advisory Committee (Box A-879)
      - Transportation Fact Sheet (Box A-879)
      - Transportation Fund, 4 folders (Box A-879)
      - Transportation Institute, 2 folders (Box A-879)
      - Transportation Legislation, 1972 (Box A-879)
      - Transportation Needs Study (Box A-879)
      - Transportation News (Box A-879)
      - Tree Removal (Box A-879)
      - Truck Transportation (Box A-879)
      - Trucks (Box A-879)
      - Trumbull Airport (Box A-879)
      - Trust Funds (Box A-879)
      - Turbo-Train (Box A-879)
      - Tweed New Haven Airport (Box A-879)
      - Unanswered Mail – S. H. Page (Box A-880)
      - United Transportation Assistance (testimony) (Box A-880)
      - Unified Transportation Assistance (UTAP) (Box A-880)
      - Unified Work Plan (Box A-880)
      - Unified Work Program (Box A-880)
      - U S #1 (Box A-880)
      - United Transportation Union (Box A-880)
      - Urban Mass Transit Administration (Box A-880)
      - Urban Mass Transportation (Box A-880)
      - Urban Systems (Box A-880)
      - Urban Transportation Fund, 1974 January 17 (Box A-880)
      - Vacancy (D.O.T.) (Box A-880)
      - Velleca, Neil A. / Access to Property (Box A-880)
      - Volpe, John A. / Secretary (Box A-880)
      - Voluntown (Box A-880)
      - Wallingford / Project (Box A-880)
      - Waring Products (Box A-880)
      - Waste (Box A-880)
      - Water Transport Assoc. (Box A-880)
      - Watertown Freight Line (Box A-880)
      - Waterways (Box A-880)
      - Waterways / Audit Report (Box A-880)
      - Westbrook Route 145 (Box A-880)
      - Westchester County Airport (Box A-880)
      - West End Division (Box A-880)
      - Westport (Box A-880)
      - Westport Bank (Box A-880)
      - Westport Post Road (Box A-880)
      - Westport Transit (Box A-880)
      - Wethersfield (Box A-880)
      - Wharton Brook Connector (Box A-880)
      - Wilbur Cross (Box A-880)
      - Wilton (Box A-880)
      - Windham Airport (Box A-880)
      - Winter Maintenance (Box A-880)
      - Wolcott Race Track (Box A-880)
      - Wood, Earl A. / Commissioner (Box A-880)
      - Wooster Square – New Haven (Box A-880)
      - Xerox (Box A-880)
  - Welfare Department (Box A-881)
    - Correspondence (Box A-881)
      - A – D (Box A-881)
      - E – L (Box A-882)
      - M – R (Box A-883)
      - S – Z (Box A-884)
    - Subject Files (Box A-885)
      - Abortion (Box A-885)
      - Adoption (Box A-885)
      - Advisory Committee (Box A-885)
      - Age of Majority (Box A-885)
      - Aging Booklet (Box A-885)
      - Allied Services (Box A-885)
      - Anonymous and "For Your Info." and No Address (Box A-885)
      - Appointments (Box A-885)
      - Appropriations Committee (Box A-885)
      - Audit Report – State Welfare Department – Payment for Ambulance Services to Welfare Recipients (Box A-885)
      - Audit Report – Welfare (Box A-885)
      - Audits (Box A-885)
      - Child Abuse (Box A-885)
      - Child Abuse Advisory Committee (Box A-885)
      - Child Development (Box A-885)
      - Child Welfare (Box A-885)
      - Child Welfare Assoc. of Conn. (Box A-885)
      - Children Study Committee (Box A-885)
      - Citizens Advisory Committee (Box A-885)
      - Conformity - Welfare (Box A-885)
      - Day Care (Box A-885)
      - “Definition of Dependent Child” – Form Letter – Public Act #625 (Box A-885)
      - Demonstrations (Box A-885)
      - District Offices (Box A-885)
      - Elderly (Box A-885)
      - Ellison (Box A-885)
      - Fair Call (Box A-885)
      - Family Assistance Plan (Box A-885)
      - Federal Takeover – January (Box A-885)
      - Flat Grant (Box A-885)
        - Mag Card (Box A-885)
        - Mag Revised, 1974 February 21 (Box A-885)
      - 1974 May 12 (Box A-885)
        - Mag Card, 1974 May 12 (Box A-885)
      - (Box A-885)
        - Mag Card YMCA (Box A-885)
        - Petition (Box A-885)
        - Revised (Box A-885)
      - Flat Grants (Box A-885)
      - Food Stamp Conference (Box A-885)
      - Food Stamps (Box A-885)
      - Foster Children (Box A-885)
      - Foster Parents (Box A-885)
      - Fraud (Box A-885)
      - Greenwich Office (Box A-886)
      - Group Homes (Box A-886)
      - HEW (Box A-886)
      - Housing (Box A-886)
      - Indian Affairs (Box A-886)
      - Letters of Support N-S (Box A-886)
      - Medical (Box A-886)
      - Memos (Box A-886)
      - Monthly Report (Box A-886)
      - New Britain Office (Box A-886)
      - News Clippings (Box A-886)
      - Norton’s Remarks, 1974 March 8 (Box A-886)
      - Norwalk (Box A-886)
      - Personnel (Box A-886)
      - Population Control (Box A-886)
      - Posted Budget Letter (Box A-886)
      - Press Releases (Box A-886)
      - Press Releases, Pamphlets, Info., etc. (Box A-886)
      - Reagan (Box A-887)
      - Regional Director's Comm. (Box A-887)
      - Reimbursements (Box A-887)
      - Reno (Box A-887)
      - Rents (Box A-887)
      - Retroactive Claims (Box A-887)
      - Sargent, Gov. Proposal (Box A-887)
      - Services and Expenditures (Box A-887)
      - Social Rehabilitation Services, 3 folders (Box A-887)
      - Social Security (Box A-887)
      - Social Services (Box A-887)
      - State Plan (Box A-887)
      - Summer Employment (Box A-887)
      - Thank You For Your Support A – M (Box A-888)
      - Thank You For Your Support N – Z (Box A-888)
      - Thorpe (Box A-888)
      - Title IV A (Box A-888)
      - Title 19 / Public Welfare (Box A-888)
      - Trips Home (Box A-888)
      - URESA (Box A-888)
      - Washington Office (Box A-888)
      - Weekly Calendar (Box A-888)
      - Welfare Legislation (Box A-888)
      - Welfare Publications (Box A-888)
      - Welfare Reform (Box A-888)
      - White, Com. (Box A-888)
      - White House Fellows (Box A-888)
      - WIN (Box A-888)
      - Women (Box A-888)
      - Work Fare (Box A-888)
      - Work Inactive Program I- Mag Letter (Box A-888)
      - World Food Crisis (Box A-888)
    - Human Rights and Opportunities Commission (Box A-889)
      - Welfare – Commission On Human Rights And Opportunities (H-Z) (Box A-889)
      - Commission On The Status Of Women, 2 folders (Box A-889)
      - Equality of Women Fact Sheet (Box A-889)
      - HRO – State Plan (Box A-889)
      - Human Rts. And Opp.: Waterbury Incident, 1972 September 17 (Box A-889)
      - Ice Storm, 1973 December (Box A-889)
      - Women Rights (Box A-889)
- Series 8. Legislative File, 1973-1974
  Correspondence, memoranda, drafts, etc. pertaining to bills before the General Assembly in the 1973 and 1974 sessions.
  Partly arranged by subject, partly by correspondent, partly unarranged.
  - Records (Box A-890 - A-891)
- Series 9. National Governors' Conference File, 1971-1974
  Correspondence and reference materials.
  Partly unarranged, partly by date, partly by subject.
  - Records (Box A-892 - A-894)
- Series 10. New England Governors' Conference File, 1971-1974
  Unarranged.
  - Records (Box A-895 - A-896)
- Series 11. New England Regional Commission File, 1971-1974
  General materials followed by subject file.
  - Records (Box A-897 - A-901)
- Series 12. Other Intergovernmental Relations Files, 1971-1974
  Includes materials on National governors' Council on Science and Technology, Republican Governors' Conference (1971-1972), Republican National Convention (1972), Tri-State Regional Planning Commission, Tri-State Transportation Commission.
  - Records (Box A-902)
- Series 13. Executive Orders, 1971-1974
  Texts of orders, 1 - 28, with some related material.
  Numerical.
  - Records (Box A-903)
- Series 14. Speeches, 1971-1974
  Texts of speeches, some with drafts and related correspondence.
  Alphabetical by subject, place, or organization addressed.
  - Abortion, 1972 May 19 (Box A-904)
  - The Advocates, 1971 May 18 (Box A-904)
  - Age of Majority, 1972 May 9 (Box A-904)
  - Aging, 1972 May 26 (Box A-904)
  - Agriculture, 1972 October 11 (Box A-904)
  - Agriculture, 1972 September 22 (Box A-904)
  - Airport Dedication, 1971 March 17 (Box A-904)
  - Alcoholism Article (Box A-904)
  - Alcoholism Conference, 1974 May 29 (Box A-904)
  - American School for the Deaf, 1972 June 14 (Box A-904)
  - American Marketing Association, Bridgeport, 1973 April 10 (Box A-904)
  - Annual Scholarship Awards: Handicapped, 1973 April 19 (Box A-904)
  - Ansonia MVD substation, 1973 October 31 (Box A-904)
  - Articles (Box A-904)
  - Basile, Dr. John X.R., Unico National dinner honoring, 1973 May 19 (Box A-904)
  - Bicentennial Message, 5/26/1905 (Box A-904)
  - Bic Pen Groundbreaking, 1973 June 28 (Box A-904)
  - Bloomfield, 1971 October 2 (Box A-904)
  - Blue Cross Testimony, 1973 August 28 (Box A-904)
  - Blue Cross Testimony, 1973 October 26 (Box A-904)
  - Bridgeport Mental Health Center, 1973 May 21 (Box A-904)
  - Budget Crisis, 1971 June 21 (Box A-904)
  - Budget Message, 1971 August 5 (Box A-904)
  - Budget Message, 1972 February 9 (Box A-904)
  - Budget Message, 1973 February 8 (Box A-904)
  - Budget Message, 1974 February 6 (Box A-904)
  - Building Codes and Standards, 1973 May 9 (Box A-904)
  - Buses, 1971 November 12 (Box A-904)
  - Buses, 1973 March 19 (Box A-904)
  - Bus Service for Elderly, 1973 May 31 (Box A-904)
  - Business and Industry, 1972 November 28 (Box A-904)
  - Calvin Bullock Forum, 1973 January 14 (Box A-904)
  - Capital Health Consortium, 1974 May 13 (Box A-904)
  - Capital Programs, 1971 June 14 (Box A-904)
  - Circuit Breaker, 1974 April (Box A-905)
  - Civil Defense, 1971 November 30 (Box A-905)
  - Civil Defense, 1972 November 28 (Box A-905)
  - Commencement Address, Notre Dame High School, 1971 June 11 (Box A-905)
  - Commencement Address, 1971 June 6 (Box A-905)